United Mine Workers of America, Legal Department records, 1909-1982 09425
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- Boyle and Yablonski, 3
  - Miners for Democracy, 1971; no content (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Post-election letters and petitions in support of UMW (arranged by district), 1970-1971; no content (Box 28, Folder 3-7)
  - Yablonski: news clippings, press releases, court documents, 1968-1971; no content (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Yablonski: news clippings, press releases, 1970-1973; no content (Box 28, Folder 9-12)
  - Tony Boyle: news clippings, 1971-1973; no content (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Albert Pass trial: news clippings, 1973; no content (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Yablonski story: Philadelphia Bulletin, 1981; no content (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Blankenship II: civil action 2186-69 (file 1 of 2), 1967-1970; no content (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Blankenship II: civil action 2186-69 (file 2 of 2), 1967-1970; no content (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69, 1969-1972; no content (Box 29, Folder 2-4)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: financial investments, 1953-1970; no content (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: financial documents, 1951-1971; no content (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: correspondence and court documents, 1969-1971; no content (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: lists of local unions maintained in districts for purpose of protecting membership of those members now working outside industry., 1961-1962; no content (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: pleadings, 1969; no content (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: statements and exhibits, 1967-1969; no content (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: Report of Committee on Hospitalization, Medical Services, and Economic Rehabilitation, 1946; no content (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: UMW Welfare and Retirement Fund correspondence and minutes, 1947-1949; no content (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Blankenship: civil action 2186-69: notes, 1969 and undated; no content (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Boyle, Owens, and Kmetz: no. 1741-71, 1969-1971; no content (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Boyle, Owens, and Kmetz: criminal case no. 346-71, 1971; no content (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Washington, D.C., grand jury, 1972; no content (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
  - Pittsburgh grand jury, 1972; no content (Box 30, Folder 5-11)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 1799-69 and D.C. Circuit Court no. 24,561 and 24,584, 1971-1972; no content (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Yablonski: D.C. Circuit Court no. 2413-69, no. 23,439, no. 23,536, no. 23,659, 1969-1974; no content (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 3061-69, 1969-1974; no content (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 1662-69 and D.C. Circuit Court no. 23,191, 1969-1974; no content (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Yablonski transcript: civil action no. 1662-69, no. 2413-69, 1969; no content (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Yablonski transcript: civil action no. 3061-69, 1969; no content (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Yablonski cases: consolidated pleadings, 1970-1972; no content (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 3436-69: backup material for interrogatory 23: lists of local unions, delegates, and expenses, 1968; no content (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 3436-69: interrogatory 24: backup material, 1967-1971; no content (Box 31, Folder 9-10)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 3436-69: interrogatories, 1970; no content (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 3436-69; Weaver: civil action no. 3436-69, 1970-1972; no content (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Yablonski: Supreme Court no. A-793, 1972; no content (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Yablonski: Supreme Court no. 72-679, 1972-1973; no content (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Yablonski: Supreme Court no. 71-1106; Boyle: civil action no. 3436-69, 1969-1976; no content (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Boyle: civil action no. 3436-69, 1969-1975; no content (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Yablonski: D.C. Circuit Court no. 24,945, appeal of civil action no. 3436-69, 1971-1975; no content (Box 32, Folder 3-5)
  - Yablonski: civil action no. 3436-69, 1970-1977; no content (Box 32, Folder 6-10)
  - James D. Hodgson: civil action no. 662-70, 1970-1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - James D. Hodgson: civil action no. 3071-64, 1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Boyle v. Kafton: docket no. 3688, 1971; no content (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Boyle v. Kafton: docket no. 3689, 1969-1971; no content (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Edward Monborne, et. al.: civil action no. 71-690, 1971; no content (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Mike Trobovich: civil action no. 1605-71, 1970-1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Mike Trobovich: civil action no. 1605-71: correspondence, 1971-1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Mike Trobovich: civil action no. 1605-71, 1971-1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Mike Trobovich: civil action no. 546-71: deposition notices, 1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Mike Trobovich: depositions, 1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Mike Trobovich: depositions, civil action no. 1605-71 and no.546-71, 1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Mike Trobovich: civil action no. 546-71: possible exhibits, 1965-1971; no content (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Mike Trobovich: civil action no. 546-71: deposition exhibits, 1970-1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Mike Trobovich: civil action no. 546-71: depositions, 1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Miners for Democracy, 1970-1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Mike Trobovich: dual unionism: civil action no. 546-71, 1973-1974; no content (Box 33, Folder 16-17)
  - Richard Weaver: Supreme Court no. 72-1747 and 72-1748, 1972; no content (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Richard Weaver: Supreme Court no. 72-1747 and 72-1748, 1972-1973; no content (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Boyle trial: transcript, 1974; no content (Box 34, Folder 2-9)
  - Boyle, Owens, and Titler: correspondence, 1973-1976; no content (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Boyle, Owens, and Titler: civil action no. 3436-69, 1975; no content (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Boyle, Owens, and Titler: civil action no. 3436-69: correspondence file on pension attachments, 1976; no content (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Boyle, Owens, and Titler: civil action no. 3436-69: appeal of Owens, 1977-1978; no content (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Boyle, Owens, and Titler: civil action no. 3436-69: attachment on pension issue, 1978; no content (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - UMW v. Boyle: no. 76-1254, 1976; no content (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - UMW v. Boyle: no. 76-1871, no. 76-1872, 1976; no content (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Louis A. Antal v. Boyle, Supreme Court no. 77-1108, 1977; no content (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, statements, and AFL chronology, 1936-1955; no content (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - National memorial period: moratorium on coal production, August 23 - September 1, 1952, no content (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Finance and negotiations documents, 1933-1961; no content (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - West Kentucky Coal Co., C. & O. Railway, and other investments, 1951-1954; no content (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
  - West Kentucky Coal Co., Cyrus Eaton, and other investments, 1955; no content (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Financial investments, 1956; no content (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - West Kentucky Coal Co. and Cyrus Eaton, 1955-1965; no content (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - West Kentucky Coal Co., 1951-1959; no content (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Financial transactions, 1957-1961; no content (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Financial transactions, 1958; no content (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - List of non-union mines received from Safety Division, 1956-1959; no content (Box 35, Folder 12-15)
  - Non-union abandonments, 1956-1959; no content (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Log of telephone calls to Boyle, 1960-1961; no content (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Boyle correspondence, 1952-1972; no content (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
  - Internal Revenue investigation, 1957; no content (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Organizations, lobbying, coal production, and other subjects, 1960-1970; no content (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Memos, 1963-1965; no content (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Statement of W. A. Boyle to House Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, 1963; no content (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Addresses and phone numbers of international union, welfare fund, and district personnel, 1969-1972; no content (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - International Executive Board correspondence, 1969-1970; no content (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - International Executive Board proceedings, 1970; no content (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - International Executive Board, 1971-1972; no content (Box 36, Folder 12-17)
  - Work stoppage reports, 1966-1969; no content (Box 36, Folder 18-20)
  - UMWA News, 1969-1971; no content (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - National fuels study, 1962-1963; no content (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - National Fuels and Energy Study Group, 1963; no content (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Southern Coal Producers Association minutes, 1951-1963; no content (Box 37, Folder 4-7)
  - Southern Coal Producers Association: deposition of Joseph E. Moody, 1969; no content (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - MA pneumonconiosis: West Virginia workmen's compensation: coal mine health and safety, 1970-1972; no content (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
  - MA pneumonconiosis: West Virginia workmen's compensation: West Virginia University, 1969-1971; no content (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration cases, 1968-1972; no content (Box 37, Folder 12-13)
  - Negotiations: Alaska contract, 1971; no content (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Black Lung Association, 1971; no content (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Coal, 1971-1972; no content (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - District 27 correspondence, 1970-1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - District 27, 1970-1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Education and drug awareness: correspondence, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Fair labor standards; coal mining safety; wages and hours, 1964-1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - "H" correspondence: Health; Hoffa, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - International Executive Board correspondence, 1963-1969; no content (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Union: Economic and Social Bulletin, vo. 16-17, 1968-1969; no content (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Booklets from international labor organizations, 1959-1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - UMW Journal, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Killion, Clarence, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Legislation, 1970-1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - John L. Lewis proposed museum, 1969; no content (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Local union leadership development conferences, manpower conferences, and legislation: correspondence and memos, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - National Coal Policy Conference: correspondence and memos, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - "O" correspondence: Occupational Health and Safety Act (OSHA) correspondence; Department of Organization correspondence, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Preventative medicine and public health correspondence, incl. black lung disease, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - "P" correspondence: Peabody Coal Co., Pennsylvania, power, production, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Research and Marketing Dept. correspondence, 1969-1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 18-19)
  - Josephine Roche, 1945-1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - "R" correspondence, incl. Jay Rockefeller coal dispute, West Virginia, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - "S" correspondence: safety, strike benefits, strip mining, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - S.M.E. Simon, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Social security, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - "U" correspondence: Udall, umpires, utilities, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Mary van Kleek, Veterans' Day, 1972; no content (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Local unions visited by district representatives, 1967-1970; no content (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
  - Boyle: outgoing president's correspondence, 1968/03-1968/08; no content (Box 39, Folder 4-9)
  - Memos, 1969/09-1971/12; no content (Box 39, Folder 10-15)
  - Support letters following Chicago meeting, 1971; no content (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Challenges to incumbents, 1964 UMW election, no content (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - UMW elections, 1964-1972; no content (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - 1972 UMW election, no content (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 1969 UMW election corresondence, no content (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
  - Post-election: Yablonski slayings and call for UMW investigations: news clips, 1969-1972; no content (Box 40, Folder 7-12)
  - Post-election: U.S. Dept. of Labor investigation and suit, UMW 1969 election, 1969-1972; no content (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Post-election: Boyle conviction, 1970-1972; no content (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Post-election: 1970 Harrison Williams Subcommittee on Labor hearings, 1970-1972; no content (Box 40, Folder 15-16)
  - Discovery documents: Big Horn Coal Co., safety conditions (District 27), Welfare and Retirement Fund (all districts), 1950-1972; no content (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - 1969 UMW election lists, no content (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Tabulation for 1969 UMW election nominations, no content (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Delegate cards, 1969; no content (Box 41)
  - Nomination forms, 1969; no content (Box 42)
  - Photocopies of election return envelopes and forms, 1969; no content (Box 43)
  - I'm Loyal to Boyle buttons, 1969; no content (Box 43)
- Photographs, 4
  - Albert Pass trial: black and white news clippings, 1973; no content (Box 44, Folder 21)